[Feature Introduction]
MusicPlayer2 is an audio player which with a collection of music playback, lyrics display, format conversion and many other functions. It supports lyrics display, lyrics karaoke style display, lyrics online download, lyrics editing, song tag recognition, album cover display, album cover online download, spectrum analysis, sound effect settings, taskbar thumbnail button, theme color, format conversion and other functions.
The playback kernel is the Bass Audio Library (V2.4).
The player supports almost all common audio formats. A detailed list of supported files is shown in the "Supported Formats" of the "Help" menu.

[Operating Instructions]
You have the following ways to open and play a song:
1. Select the "Open File" item on the File menu;
2. Select the "Open folder" item on the File menu;
3. Click the "Select Folder" button or select the "Select Folder" item on the "Tools" menu, select a recently played folder in the popped up dialog, or click the "Open new folder" button to play a new folder;
4. Drag and drop the file or folder directly into the main window of the program;
5. Drag and drop the file or folder directly onto the program's icon or its shortcut icon.

[Shortcut key description]
Play/Pause: Spaces
Previous Song: V
Next Song: N
Fast Forward for 5 sec: Right
Rewind for 5 Seconds: Left
Volume Up: Up
Volume Down: Down
Switch Repeat Mode: M
Quick Find: F
Select Folder: Ctrl+T
Find Songs: Ctrl+F
Open File Location: Ctrl+B
Option Settings: Ctrl+I
Open File: Ctrl+O
Open Folder: Ctrl+D
Lyrics Adjustment: Ctrl+PgUp/Ctrl+PgDn
Save Lyrics Adjustment: Ctrl+S
Mini Mode: Ctrl+M
Track Information: Ctrl+N
Sound Effect Settings: Ctrl+E
Full Screen: F11
Show/Hide playlist: Ctrl+L
Float playlist: Ctrl+K

[Mouse Action]
- Use mouse wheel to adjust volume.
- Hold Shift and click the right mouse button to pop up the system menu.

[Troubleshooting]
- If you encountered that the player can't play with the speaker after unplugging your headset, or it still play with the speakers after plugging in your headset, and opening any song shows an error in playback, by clicking "Reinitialize Player" in the "Tools" menu can resolve this problem.